若你打开在教师笔记中的XML可视化器的链接
If you open up the link to the XML visualizer, that we provided
这就是你将看到的
you in the instructor notes, then this is what it would look like.
我们有一个线性布局 里面有显示为Guest List的TextView
We have a linear layout with a text view that says Guest List and
和显示为Kunal的TextView
another text view that says Kunal.
第一个任务是在Guest List下加入更多的TextView
The first task was to add more text views to create the guest list.
那么我们就复制粘贴这个XML元素
So let's copy and paste this XML element.
好 现在加入一些其他人
Cool, let's add some other people besides Kunal.
我们加入Kagure和Lyla
Let's add Kagure and also Lyla.
棒
Awesome.
那么现在Kagure和Lyla在Kunal的名字下面
So now Kagure and Lyla show up under Kunal's name.
我们也可以改变任何现成的文字
We can also change any of the existing text use.
我们把它变成VIP名单
We change to the VIP list.
第二个任务是把方向属性改成水平的
The second task was to change the orientation attribute to be horizontal.
这立刻把所有的TextView从纵向排列
This immediately changes all the text views to appear side by side
改为并排的
instead of one on top of the other.